Karen Shearer Collection, 1935-1996, bulk 1974-1992
Indiana University Digital Library Program
- 2. Rock Chronicles (radio program), 1967-1996
  - 2.2. Rock Chronicles Publicity Materials and Photographs, 1935-1996, bulk 1980-1996
    - Rankin, Billy, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Ratt (Musical group), 1984, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Rave-ups (Musical group), 1989, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Raw Youth (Musical group), 1991, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Raye, Julianna, undated, Publicity materials
    - Rea, Chris, 1951-, 1988-1990, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Real Life (Musical group), 1983-1984, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Reckless Sleepers (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Red 7 (Musical group), 1985, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Red Box (Musical group), 1987, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Red Hot Chili Peppers (Musical group), 1991, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Red House (Musical group), 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Red House Painters (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Red Rider (Musical group); Cochrane, Tom, 1983-1986, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Red Rockers (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Red Siren (Musical group), 1989, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Red Wave (MTV Special), undated, 7 photographs + publicity materials about Russian rock bands
    - Redd, Toby, undated, Publicity materials
    - Reed, Lou, 1988, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Re-flex (Musical group), 1984, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Refugee (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Reivers (Musical group), 1987-1989, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - REO Speedwagon (Musical group), 1886-1991, 5 photographs + publicity materials
    - Repercussions (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Replacements (Musical group), 1987-1990, 4 photographs + publicity materials
    - Return 2 Zero (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Revenge (Musical group), 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Reyne, James, 1988, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Rheostatics, 1994, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Rhino Bucket (Musical group), 1990-1992, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Rhythm Corps (Musical group), 1988, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Richman, Jonathan, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Ride (Musical group), 1990-1994, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Ridgeley, Andrew, 1963-, 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Ridgeway, Stan, 1989, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Rigor Mortis (Musical group), 1988, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Riot (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Ritenour, Lee, 1984, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - River City People (Musical group), 1990, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Riverdogs (Musical group), 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Roaring Boys (Musical group), 1986, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Roberts, Kane, 1991, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Robertson, Robbie, 1987-1991, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Roches (Musical group), 1989, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Rock & Hyde (Musical group), 1987, 1 photograph, + publicity materials
    - Rock City Angels (Musical group), 1988, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Rock Goddess (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Rockapella (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Rockets (Musical group: Michigan), 1983, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Rodriguez, Silvio, undated, Publicity materials
    - Rogers, Paul, 1983-1984, Publicity materials
    - Rolie, Gregg, 1987, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Rolling Stones, 1978-1989, 5 photographs + publicity materials
    - Rollings, Matt, 1989, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Roman Holliday (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Romantics (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Romeo Void (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Ronstadt, Linda, 1986-1989, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Rossington Collins Band, 1981, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Roth, David Lee, 1955-, 1990-1994, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Roxette (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Roxy Music (Musical group), 1980s, Publicity materials
    - Royal Court of China (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Royal Crescent Mob (Musical group), 1989-1991, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Rozum, Alex, 1988, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - RPLA (Musical group), 1994, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Rubinoos (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Ruefrex (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Ruffner, Mason, 1985, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Rundgren, Todd, 1991, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Rush (Musical group), 1980-1989, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Rush, Jennifer, 1986, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Rutherford, Mike, 1989, Publicity materials
    - Ryder, Gene, 1989, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Ryser, Jimmy, 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Saga (Musical group), 1981-1985, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Saint Etienne (Musical group), undated, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Saint-Marie, Buffy, circa 1975, 7 photographs + publicity materials
    - Salty Dog (Musical group), 1989, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Samples (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Sanborn, David, 1988, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Sanctuary (Musical group), 1989, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Sandée, undated, Publicity materials
    - Santana (Musical group), 1985-1991, 6 photographs + publicity materials
    - Saraya (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Sarde, Cliff, undated, Publicity materials
    - Satriani, Joe, 1988-1989, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Saxon (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Scaggs, Boz, 1944-, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Schascle (Musician), 1991, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Schenker, Michael, 1980s, Publicity materials
    - Schilling, Peter, 1983-1989, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Schmit, Timothy B., undated, Publicity materials
    - Schmitt, Adam, 1991-1993, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Schon, Neal, 1989, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - School of Fish (Musical group), 1991, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Scialfa, Patti, 1993, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Scofield, John, circa 1986, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Scorpions (Musical group), 1984-1990, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Scott, Jef, undated, Publicity materials
    - Scott, Raymond, undated, Publicity materials
    - Scott, Tim, undated, Publicity materials
    - Scott, Tom, 1948-, 1982, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Scotti, Nic, undated, Publicity materials
    - Screaming Blue Messiahs (Musical group), 1989, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Screaming Jets (Musical group), 1991, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Screaming Trees (Musical group), 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Scritti Politti (Musical group), 1988, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Sealand Poets (Musical group), 1993, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Seals & Crofts, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Seals, Dan, undated, Publicity materials
    - Seduce (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - See No Evil (Musical group), 1989-1990, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Seger, Bob, 1980-1991, 5 photographs + publicity materials
    - Seiko (Musical performer), 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Sembello, Michael, 1983-1984, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Semi-Twang (Musical group), 1988, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Senseless Things (Musical group), 1991, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Sequal, 1988, Publicity materials
    - Setzer, Brian, 1988, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Sevelle, Taja, 1991, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Seven Stories (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Sex Pistols (Musical group), 1987, Publicity materials
    - Sexton, Charlie, 1986-1989, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Shadowfax (Musical group), 1988, 1 photograph + publicity materials (Box 58)
    - Shadowland (Musical group), 1989-1990, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Shaffer, Paul, 1989, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Shakatak (Musical group), 1989, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Shaking Family (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Shamen (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Shankar, Ravi, 1920-, undated, Publicity materials
    - Shannon, Del, 1980s, Publicity materials
    - Shark Island (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Sharkey, Feargal, 1985, Publicity materials
    - Sharp, Todd, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Shaw, Tommy, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Shaw-Blades (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Shear, Jules, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Shell & the Crush (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Shelley, Pete, undated, Publicity materials
    - Shelleyan Orphan (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Shepard, Vonda, 1989, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Sheriff (Musical group), 1988, Publicity materials
    - Shinas, Sofia, 1992, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Shine (Musical group), 1989, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Shocked, Michelle, 1988-1992, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Shok Paris (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Shooting Star (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Show of Hands (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Shrieve, Michael, undated, Publicity materials
    - Shumov, Vasily, undated, Publicity materials
    - Shy England (Musical group), 1989, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Siberry, Jane, 1988-1993, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Silencers (Musical group), 1987, Publicity materials
    - Silverstein, Shel, 1985, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Simon and Garfunkel, 1981-1990, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Simon F., 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Simon, Carly, 1980s, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Simon, Fred, undated, Publicity materials
    - Simone, 1988, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Simple Minds (Musical group), 1994-1995, 4 photographs + publicity materials
    - Simply Red (Musical group), 1987-1989, 4 photographs + publicity materials
    - Sinatra, Frank, 1915-1998, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Siouxsie & the Banshees (Musical group), 1986-1995, 4 photographs + publicity materials
    - Siren (Musical group), 1989, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Sister Whiskey (Musical group), 1993, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Sisters of Mercy (Musical group), 1990, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Skagarack (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Skid Row (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Skinny Boys (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Skinny Puppy (Musical group), 1987-1990, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Skiploader (Musical group), 1995, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Skipworth & Turner, undated, Publicity materials
    - Skyliners (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Skywalk (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Slade (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Slash (Musician), undated, Publicity materials
    - Slaughter (Musical group), 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Slayer (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Slick, Grace, 1980, Publicity materials
    - Sluggers (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Smash Palace (Musical group), 1985, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Smashed Gladys (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Smashing Pumpkins (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Smith, Darden, 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Smith, Joe (former President of Capitol./EMI), undated, Publicity materials
    - Smith, Michael W. (Michael Whitaker), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Smith, Patti; Scandal (Musical group), 1975-1988, 4 photographs + publicity materials
    - Smithereens (Musical group), 1986-1991, 5 photographs + publicity materials
    - Smiths (Musical group), 1987, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - So (Musical group), 1988, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Sobule, Jill, 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Social Distortion (Musical group), 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Soft Cell (Musical group), 1982, Publicity materials
    - Some, Belouis, 1985-1987, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Sonic Youth (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Sons of Angels (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Soul Asylum (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Soul Family Sensation (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Soulhat (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Soundgarden (Musical group), 1994, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Soup Dragons (Musical group), 1988, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Souther, J.D., 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Southside Johnny, 1980, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Space Monkey (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Spandau Ballet (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Spanos, Danny, undated, Publicity materials
    - Sparks (Musical group), 1983, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Spence, Brian, 1988, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Spence, Judson, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Spin Doctors (Musical group), 1991, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Spinal Tap (Musical group), 1984, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Spirit (Musical group), 1982-1991, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Split Enz (Musical group), 1981-1984, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Sponge (Musical group), 1994-1995, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Spoons (Musical group), 1988, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Springfield, Rick, 1980s, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Springsteen, Bruce, 1980-1995, 4 photographs + publicity materials
    - Squeeze (Musical group), 1982, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Squier, Billy, 1984-1989, Publicity materials
    - St. Johnny (Musical group), 1995, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - St. Paul (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Stabilizers (Musical group), 1986, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Stamey, Chris, undated, Publicity materials
    - Stanley, Michael, undated, Publicity materials
    - Stansfield, Lisa, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Starship (Musical group), 1980-1989, 4 photographs + publicity materials
    - Stealin Horses (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Steele, Maureen, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Steely Dan (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Steinfeld, Jake, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Stephenson, Martin; Daintees (Musical group), 1990, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Stephenson, Van, 1984, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Steps Ahead (Musical group); Mainieri, Mike, 1989, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Stevens, Steve, 1989, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Stewart, Dave, 1980s, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Stewart, John, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Stewart, Rod, 1989-1991, 4 photographs + publicity materials
    - Stigers, Curtis, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Sting (Musician), 1984-1987, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Stompers (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Stone Free (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Stone Fury (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Stone Roses (Musical group), 1993-1995, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Stone Temple Pilots (Musical group), 1994, Publicity materials
    - Straitjacket Fits (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Strange Advance (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Stranglers (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Strata Institute (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Stray Cats (Musical group), 1983-1989, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Street, Janey, 1984, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Streisand, Barbra, 1988-1991, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Stress (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Style Council (Musical group), 1986-1988, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Styx (Musical group), 1980-1981, Publicity materials
    - Suburbs (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials (Box 59)
    - Suddenly, Tammy! (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Suede (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Sugarcubes (Musical group), 1980s, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Suicidal Tendencies (Musical group), 1988-1990, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Summer, Andy, 1980s, Publicity materials
    - Summer, Henry Lee, 1989-1993, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Sun and the Moon (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Sun-60 (Musical group), 1993, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Sundays (Musical group), 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Sunscreen (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Super 8 (Musical group), 1995-1996, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Supertramp (Musical group), 1980s, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Supreme Love Gods (Musical group), 1992, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Survivor (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Swans (Musical group), 1989, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Sweet Lizard Illtet (Musical group), 1992, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Sweet, Matthew, 1964-, 1993-1995, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Swimming Pool Q's (Musical group), 1989, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Swing Out Sister (Musical group), 1987-1989, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - T42 (Musical group), 1991, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Tackhead (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Taff, Russ, 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Talk Talk (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Talking Heads (Musical group), 1986-1988, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Tall Stories (Musical group), 1991, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Taupin, Bernie, 1980, Publicity materials
    - Taxxi (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Taylor, Andy, 1987, Publicity materials
    - Taylor, Derek, 1985, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Taylor, Greg (Greg Fingers), 1989, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Taylor, James, 1948-, 1985-1993, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Taylor, Les, 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Taylor, Steve, 1993, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Taylor, Susanne Jerome, undated, Publicity materials
    - Tears for Fears (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Teenage Fanclub (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Television (Musical group), 1992, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Ten Sharp (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Ten Ten (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Tenderloin (Musical group), 1994, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Tepper, Robert, 1986, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Terrell (Musician), 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Tesla (Musical group), 1987-1991, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Texas Tornados (Musical group), 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Textones (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - The (Musical group), 1994, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Then Jerico (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - They Might Be Giants (Musical group), 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Thieves (Musical group), 1988, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Thin Lizzy (Musical group), 1991, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Thomas, B.J., undated, Publicity materials
    - Thompson Twins (Musical group), 1989-1991, 6 photographs + publicity materials
    - Thompson, Marc Anthony, undated, Publicity materials
    - Thompson, Richard, 1988, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Thorogood, George, 1985-1988, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Three (Musical group), 1988, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Three O'Clock (Musical group), 1988, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Throbs (Musical group), 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Throwing Muses (Musical group), 1987-1989, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Thunder (Musical group), 1989-1991, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Tiffany, 1971-, 1989, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Tikaram, Tanita, 1988-1992, 5 photographs + publicity materials
    - 'Til Tuesday (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Timbuk 3 (Musical group), 1986, 2 photographs + publicity materials
    - Time Bandits (Musical group), 1985, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Time Machine (Musical group), 1989, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Tiny Lights (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Tirez Tirez (Musical group), 1987, Publicity materials
    - Titiyo (Musician), undated, Publicity materials
    - TNT (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Toad the Wet Sprocket (Musical group), 1989-1991, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Toll (Musical group), 1988, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Tom Tom Club (Musical group), 1989, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Tomlinson, Michael, undated, Publicity materials
    - Too Much Joy (Musical group), 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Tool (Musical group), 1993-1994, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Tora Tora (Musical group), 1980s, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Torch Song (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Toronto (Musical group), undated, Publicity materials
    - Toto (Musical group), 1979-1990, 4 photographs + publicity materials
    - Toups, Wayne, 1958-; Zydecajun (Musical group), 1991, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Tovey, Frank, 1986, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Tower of Power (Musical group), 1991, 3 photographs + publicity materials
    - Townshend, Pete, 1972-1980, Publicity materials
    - Toy Matinee (Musical group), 1990, 1 photograph + publicity materials
    - Toy Subs (Musical group), 1991, Publicity materials